<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Joraskie</title>
    <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eric Joraskie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ericjoraskie.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Eric Joraskie and I am a computer science graduate student at Northeastern University.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had an unusual path into CS. Prior to a string of injuries resulting in my football career prematurely coming to an end, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d end up playing in the NFL. Upon medically retiring from football toward the end of my sophomore year at Northwestern University, I began to focus my studies on neuroscience, which I found to be exciting enough to keep my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Athletics</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/athletics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/athletics/</guid>
      <description>Having played football for 16 years and having been a full scholarship athlete at Northwestern, I&amp;rsquo;m often met with surprise when people find out I don&amp;rsquo;t watch or follow any sports. So, although I can definitely talk about sports generally, if you were to ask me something specific about a player or team, it is likely I will not have the answer.
However, I do enjoy being an athlete. For fun, here is my high school highlight tape:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/blog/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Right Path</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/posts/finding_the_right_path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/posts/finding_the_right_path/</guid>
      <description>I graduated from Northwestern with a degree in neuroscience. The reason I studied neuro was questionable by educational investment standards: I thought it was really cool.
After I medically retired from football, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really sure what to do with myself. The college athlete experience is a different conversation entirely, so I&amp;rsquo;ll save it for another post, but having grown up in small central Pennsylvania town where football was pretty much the only thing people had or cared about, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t spent tons of time considering life after football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/photography/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated with photography since I was a kid.*
Luckily for me, my high school had a TV Studio extracurricular that gave me the opportunity to spend a lot of time using DSLRs, shoulder-mount video cameras and a few different professional photo and video editing softwares, so I was able to get a reasonable amount of practice fairly early on.
Now I mainly use a DJI Mavic Air 2, a Sony Cybershot that is a few years old but still great, and I have a Rylo (r.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve written a lot of code and enjoy writing code, so that volume is growing. That being said, I&amp;rsquo;m relatively selective about what I keep in a public repository. Here are a couple of projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on with links to what is available. I will update this page as I make more code available on GitHub.
 Othello   Optical Escape  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/</guid>
      <description>I read a lot.
It&amp;rsquo;s usually nonfiction but I&amp;rsquo;ve included some of my favorite novels too. Here is a quick list of eight of my favorites I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to risk my recommendation reputation on.
I&amp;rsquo;ve linked them all to their page on Goodreads and the authors are linked to the best info source I could quickly find.
I&amp;rsquo;m actually not really a fan of Goodreads (mainly their web page design; I think their pages are very cluttered), but I figured it was better than linking directly to Amazon, although I understand it&amp;rsquo;s only really one additional step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videography</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/videography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/videography/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>