<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Joraskie</title>
    <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eric Joraskie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ericjoraskie.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal site! I&amp;rsquo;m currently an AI Researcher at JHUAPL.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had an unusual path into AI research. Toward the end of my sophomore year at Northwestern University, injuries brought my football career to an early conclusion. I turned my attention to neuroscience, and after falling in love with the subject, I contemplated both the pursuit of a Ph.D. in neuroscience, and medical school, at different points throughout my senior year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Athletics</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/athletics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/athletics/</guid>
      <description>Having played football for 16 years and having been a full scholarship athlete at Northwestern, I&amp;rsquo;m often met with surprise when people find out I don&amp;rsquo;t watch or follow any sports. So, although I can definitely talk about sports generally, if you were to ask me something specific about a player or team, it is likely I will not have the answer.
However, I do enjoy being an athlete. For fun, here is my high school highlight tape:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/blog/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/music/</guid>
      <description>During my freshman year at Northwestern (2013), I became interested in digital music production.
I purchased a MIDI device, the M-Audio Keystation Mini 32, because it was the cheapest and smallest one I could find, and it came with a simple software called Ignite, which I used to make loops. I was gifted a copy of Sony ACID Music studio (a Digital Audio Workstation) and developed a process where after creating instrumental loops in Ignite, I would open them in ACID to polish them into a full piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Suggested Reads</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/othersuggestedreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/othersuggestedreads/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/photography/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated with photography since I was a kid.*
Luckily for me, my high school had a TV Studio extracurricular that gave me the opportunity to spend a lot of time using DSLRs, shoulder-mount video cameras and a few different professional photo and video editing softwares, so I was able to get a reasonable amount of practice fairly early on.
Now I mainly use a DJI Mavic Air 2, a Sony Cybershot that is a few years old but still great, and I have a Rylo (r.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve written a lot of code and enjoy writing code, so that volume is growing. That being said, I&amp;rsquo;m relatively selective about what I keep in a public repository. Here are a couple of projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on with links to what is available. I will update this page as I make more code available on GitHub.
Grand Canyon Traffic Detection This project originated from a quick drive I wanted to take up to the Grand Canyon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/readinglist/</guid>
      <description>I read a lot. (A more extensive list can be found here)
It&amp;rsquo;s usually nonfiction but I&amp;rsquo;ve included some of my favorite novels too. Here is a short list containing eight of my favorites I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to risk my recommendation reputation on.
Previously, I&amp;rsquo;d linked all of the titles to their page on Goodreads, but I despise how cluttered the site is and have since discovered StoryGraph; it&amp;rsquo;s an up-and-coming competitor which supports Bookshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videography</title>
      <link>https://ericjoraskie.com/videography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericjoraskie.com/videography/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>